[
    {
        "uid": "032201",
        "question": "Is your selected PPE constructed from materials that are compatible with the chemicals you’re using? (Link to material compatibility, e.g. www.coleparmer.com/chemical-resistance)",
        "answer": "General (For all PPE)"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032202",
        "question": "Are you working with large quantities of chemicals which are high skin adsorbant, skin/eye irritants and may splash during the experiment? (Larger quantities of liquid)",
        "answer": "Chemical splash goggles, chemical-resistant lab coat"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032203",
        "question": "Are you working with large quantities of chemicals which are skin irritants, there is a skin absorption risk leading to other hazards (organ damage, etc.), which may splash during the experiment?\nAre you working with high pressure systems, pressurized equipment, or in other scenarios where there is a potential for rupture, splash, spray or risk of flying debris?",
        "answer": "Face shield"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032204",
        "question": "Are you working with lasers or other sources of intense radiation?",
        "answer": "Shaded goggles"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032205",
        "question": "Are you working with flammable or other pyrophoric reagents?\nAre you working with open flames or other significant sources of heat/energy?",
        "answer": "Flame-resistant lab coat, flame resistant gloves"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032206",
        "question": "Are you working with explosive/energetic materials?",
        "answer": "Fire/explosion resistant gear"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032207",
        "question": "Are you working with larger quantities of extremely hazardous chemicals which may spill or splash? (e.g., acid digestion procedures)",
        "answer": "Chemical resistant apron (over lab coat), shoe covers, gloves for heavy chemical protection"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032208",
        "question": "Are you working with heavy items which may be dropped onto your feet?",
        "answer": "Steel-toed boots/hard boots"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032209",
        "question": "Are you working with large volumes of chemicals that have significant corrosive, reactive, skin contact, carcinogenic or reproductive hazards with the potential of splash or spill?",
        "answer": "Heavy chemical protection gloves (e.g. thicker nitrile, rubber, SilverShield)"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032210",
        "question": "Are you working with hot materials (>60°C) that have the potential of scalding?",
        "answer": "Heat resistant gloves"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032211",
        "question": "Are you working with very cold materials (<0°C) or cryogens?",
        "answer": "Cryogenic protection gloves"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032212",
        "question": "Are you working with sharps (e.g., broken glass, needles) that have a puncture risk? \nAre you working with cutting, grinding, or drilling tools.",
        "answer": "Cut/Puncture resistant gloves"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032213",
        "question": "Are you working with powered electrical equipment in a manner that there is risk of shock hazards?",
        "answer": "Electrical shock resistant gloves"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032214",
        "question": "Are you working in the presence of materials that can form fine particles of suspended dust that can be inhaled?",
        "answer": "Dust and particulates mask (e.g. N95)"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032215",
        "question": "Are you working with potentially airborne pathogens, hazardous gases, or volatile/aerosolized chemicals that may pose a serious toxicity or other inhalation hazard?",
        "answer": "Full-face or half-face respirators"
    },
    {
        "uid": "032216",
        "question": "Are you working in an environment with more than 70 dB of noise? (Ex: lawnmower). Consider doubling up on hearing protection for noises over 120 dB.",
        "answer": "Over-ear and/or in-ear protection"
    }
]
